segger.com 2017-11-13

# Privacy Policy | SEGGER - The Embedded Experts

### By using a SEGGER website, you consent to the collection and use of your data in the manner and for the purposes set out below. Any personal information which may be collected from a SEGGER website will be treated in accordance with this privacy policy. 

#### What personal information is collected when visiting the SEGGER website?

When you visit a SEGGER website, we may collect personal information, including name, title, company, mailing address, email address, phone numbers, fax numbers and our web server logs, browser cookies and local shared objects may collect details of your domain name, operating system, browser type, IP address and a unique identifier for your computer, or other access device (“data”). When you submit data you are agreeing to its transfer, storage and processing. 

#### What personal information is collected when subscribing to the SEGGER newsletter?

Our website offers the opportunity to subscribe to SEGGER notifications. You can select by check boxes for which products you would like to receive news. You need to provide a valid email address. When subscribing to our newsletter, we will store your name, company name, email address, IP address as well as the date and time you subscribed. We will not collect any other data. The data thereby collected is used solely for the purpose of providing you with the related product news. You may cancel your subscription to the newsletter at any time. You will find additional details in the email confirming your subscription as well as in each newsletter. 

#### What personal information is collected when registering an account at SEGGER?

Our website offers the opportunity to register a user account in order to get access to software downloads from our web server. Some information such as your email address, first name, last name, country, company name and city are mandatory, others such as address, zip / postal code, job title and work phone are optional. When registering an account, we will store your submitted information, IP address as well as the date and time you subscribed We will not collect any other data. The data thereby collected is used solely for the purpose of providing you with the related product news. 

#### What personal information is collected when purchasing through SEGGER's web shop?

When you purchase through SEGGER web shop, we collect personal information, including name, company, mailing address, email address, phone numbers, fax numbers and our web server logs, browser cookies and local shared objects may collect details of your domain name, operating system, browser type, IP address and a unique identifier for your computer, or other access device. When you submit data you are agreeing to its transfer, storage and processing. We process data in the ordinary course of business, including using outside companies to ship orders. If you pay for products by credit, we store the name of the credit card holder as well as the last 4 digits of the credit card number. 

#### Who is collecting the data?

When you are on a SEGGER website and are asked for data, you are sharing that data with SEGGER and its subsidiaries. The SEGGER website may also contain various links to third-party web sites. Third-party web sites may provide additional information, goods, services and/or promotions. These sites are owned and operated independently from us, and have their own separate privacy and data collection practices. Any data you provide to these web sites will be governed under the terms of their privacy policy, if any. We have no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the independent actions or policies of these independent sites, and are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such sites. 

#### How is your data used?

Data may be used internally by us, including updating our databases, contacting you, maintaining a technical support history or sending marketing or sales information for SEGGER products. 

#### With whom do we share your data?

Except as expressly stated in this policy or on our web sites, we do not provide your data to third parties without your consent. If you request information regarding SEGGER products provided by a Distributor of SEGGER we will share your data with our approved distributor in your country and they will supply you with the requested information. If you register and provide information to the SEGGER forum or SEGGER blog the information you provide will be publicly available. We may use third parties to provide services on our behalf, including promotions or marketing. We may provide your relevant data to them solely for the purposes of the effective delivery of such services. We may use your data if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of SEGGER, our customers, or others. 

#### What choices do you have regarding the collection, use and distribution of your data?

We may, from time to time, send you an email regarding our products and services. If you do not want to receive such information, simply tell us when you give us your data, or follow the directions contained on the mailing to remove your name from our mailing list(s). You also have the right to access (review, correct, amend or delete) your data by contacting us. Individuals are responsible for providing SEGGER with accurate and complete personal information, and for contacting us if correction of such information is required. Please direct any questions concerning SEGGER's privacy practices or if you have any queries or requests in relation to your data to infosegger com.

#### How secure is your data?

We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving . We have appropriate security measures in place to protect against any loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected. However, we cannot ensure or otherwise warrant the security of any information you provide to us or from a SEGGER website, and therefore you use the SEGGER website at your own risk. 

#### What about browser cookies and local shared objects?

We may collect and store information about your visit to our web site automatically using browser cookies (files which are sent by us to your computer) or similar devices which we can access when you visit our web site in future. We may also use local shared objects, sometimes known as Adobe Flash cookies, to remember settings, preferences and usage similar to browser cookies. The SEGGER website uses Google Analytics, a web analytic service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of the SEGGER website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. If you want to stop browser cookies being stored on your computer in future or if you want to delete any browser cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to your browser manufacturer's instructions by clicking "Help" in your browser menu.. Please note that by deleting or disabling browser cookies or local shared objects you may not be able to use certain areas or features of the SEGGER website. 

#### Changes to this privacy policy

We may revise this privacy policy at any time by amending this page. You are expected to check this page from time to time to take notice of any changes we made, as they are binding on you. Some of the provisions contained in this privacy policy may also be superseded by provisions or notices published elsewhere on our site. 

Thank you for visiting our site. SEGGER Microcontroller GmbH & Co. KG
